<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Irani Tour</string>
    <string name="app_shoar" translatable="false">Irani Tour is your good companion :)</string>
    <string name="saved_locations" translatable="false">Saved locations</string>
    <string name="about_us" translatable="false">About us</string>
    <string name="setting" translatable="false">Setting</string>
    <string name="change_themes" translatable="false">Change Themes</string>
    <string name="open_drawer" translatable="false">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer" translatable="false">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="iranology" translatable="false">Iranology</string>
    <string name="land_mark" translatable="false">Land Mark</string>
    <string name="profile" translatable="false">Profile</string>
    <string name="exit" translatable="false">Exit</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="retry" translatable="false">Retry...</string>
    <string name="next" translatable="false">Next</string>
    <string name="close" translatable="false">Close</string>
    <string name="no_internet" translatable="false">No Network Connection</string>
    <string name="full_name" translatable="false">Full Name</string>
    <string name="user_name" translatable="false">User Name</string>
    <string name="gmail" translatable="false">Gmail</string>
    <string name="password" translatable="false">Password</string>
    <string name="re_password" translatable="false">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up" translatable="false">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="error_8_password" translatable="false">Password must be at least 8 characters long</string>
    <string name="password_not_match" translatable="false">Password does not match</string>
    <string name="fill_value" translatable="false">Please fill in all the values</string>
    <string name="enter_password" translatable="false">Please enter password</string>


    <!-- Ostan name -->
    <string name="east_azarbaijan" translatable="false">East Azarbaijan</string>
    <string name="west_azarbaijan" translatable="false">West Azarbaijan</string>
    <string name="ardabil" translatable="false">Ardabil</string>
    <string name="esfahan" translatable="false">Esfahan</string>
    <string name="alborz" translatable="false">Alborz</string>
    <string name="ilam" translatable="false">Ilam</string>
    <string name="bushehr" translatable="false">Bushehr</string>
    <string name="tehran" translatable="false">Tehran</string>
    <string name="chahar_mahal_bakhtiari" translatable="false">Chahar Mahal Bakhtiari</string>
    <string name="south_khorasan" translatable="false">South Khorasan</string>
    <string name="north_khorasan" translatable="false">North Khorasan</string>
    <string name="khorasan_razavi" translatable="false">Khorasan Razavi</string>
    <string name="khozestan" translatable="false">Khozestan</string>
    <string name="zanjan" translatable="false">Zanjan</string>
    <string name="semnan" translatable="false">Semnan</string>
    <string name="sistan_baluchistan" translatable="false">Sistan Baluchistan</string>
    <string name="fars" translatable="false">Fars</string>
    <string name="qazvin" translatable="false">Qazvin</string>
    <string name="qom" translatable="false">Qom</string>
    <string name="kurdistan" translatable="false">Kurdistan</string>
    <string name="kerman" translatable="false">Kerman</string>
    <string name="kermanshah" translatable="false">Kermanshah</string>
    <string name="kohgiloyeh_and_boyerahmad" translatable="false">Kohgiloyeh and Boyerahmad</string>
    <string name="golestan" translatable="false">Golestan</string>
    <string name="gilan" translatable="false">Gilan</string>
    <string name="lorestan" translatable="false">Lorestan</string>
    <string name="mazandaran" translatable="false">Mazandaran</string>
    <string name="markazi" translatable="false">Markazi</string>
    <string name="hormozgan" translatable="false">Hormozgan</string>
    <string name="hamedan" translatable="false">Hamedan</string>
    <string name="yazd" translatable="false">Yazd</string>
    <string name="entekhab_ostan" translatable="false">Select the desired province</string>
    <string name="edit" translatable="false">Edit</string>
    <string name="cancel" translatable="false">Cancel</string>
    <string name="edit_data" translatable="false">Information changed successfully</string>

    <!-- Ostan Details -->
    <string name="east_azarbaijan_detail" translatable="false">East Azerbaijan Province is one of the central provinces of Iran, boasting a plethora of tourist, historical, cultural, and industrial attractions. Its capital city, Tabriz, with a population of over one million, stands as one of Iran\'s largest cities and serves as the most important industrial and commercial center in the northwest of Iran. East Azerbaijan Province shares borders with West Azerbaijan Province to the north, Ardabil Province to the east, Zanjan Province to the south, and West Azerbaijan Province again to the west.\nThe province has a diverse climate, with parts being mountainous and cold, while others enjoy a semi-humid and moderate climate. Moreover, East Azerbaijan Province is home to areas with beautiful wetlands, lakes, and waterfalls such as Lake Urmia and Sahand Waterfall, which provide numerous tourist attractions for visitors.\nThe province is also significant in terms of industry and agriculture. Industries such as food processing, textiles, steel, automotive manufacturing, and petrochemicals play vital roles in the province\'s economy. Alongside industry, agriculture is well-developed in this province, with diverse productions of agricultural products including wheat, saffron, apples, and grapes.\nCulturally, East Azerbaijan Province boasts a rich history and culture. Its people speak Azerbaijani Turkish and adhere to their own traditions, music, and local arts. Each year, various festivals, exhibitions, and cultural activities are held in this province, contributing to the promotion of the region\'s culture and art.</string>
    <string name="west_azarbaijan_details" translatable="false">West Azerbaijan Province is one of the western provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 37,497 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in Iran. It shares borders with East Azerbaijan Province to the north, Zanjan Province to the east, Hamedan and Kermanshah Provinces to the south, and Iraq to the west.\nThe capital of West Azerbaijan Province is Urmia, with a population of over 1.7 million, making it one of Iran\'s largest cities. Urmia serves as a melting pot of different cultures and boasts numerous tourist attractions, including Lake Urmia, the Urmia-Tehran highway, and Zarineh Sardasht Waterfall.\nWest Azerbaijan Province is recognized as one of the important agricultural regions of Iran. Its agricultural productions include wheat, barley, apples, walnuts, and grapes. Additionally, processing and food industries have developed in this province, playing a significant role in the regional economy.\nCulturally, West Azerbaijan Province has a rich history and culture. Its people speak Azerbaijani Turkish and cherish their traditions, music, and local arts. Every year, various festivals and cultural activities are held in this province, contributing to the promotion of the region\'s culture and art.</string>
    <string name="ardabil_details" translatable="false">Ardabil Province is one of the northwestern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 18,031 square kilometers, making it one of the significant provinces in Iran. It shares borders with the Republic of Azerbaijan to the north, Gilan Province to the east, Zanjan Province to the south, and West Azerbaijan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Ardabil Province is Ardabil city, with a population of over 690,000, making it one of the major cities in northwest Iran. The city boasts numerous tourist attractions, including the shrine of Imamzadeh Ismail, the shrine of Imamzadeh Seyyed Ahmad, and Shorabil Waterfall.\nArdabil Province has a diverse climate, with cold winters and moderate summers. Its forests, lakes, and beautiful waterfalls are among the natural attractions that attract many tourists.\nTourism, agriculture, and animal husbandry are among the important economic activities in Ardabil Province. Its agricultural products include wheat, apples, cherries, and cabbage.\nCulturally, Ardabil Province has a rich cultural and historical heritage. Its people speak Azerbaijani Turkish and cherish their traditions, music, and local arts. Additionally, various cultural festivals and events are held in this province every year, contributing to the promotion of the region\'s culture and art</string>
    <string name="esfahan_details" translatable="false">Isfahan Province is one of the central provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 107,000 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Qazvin and Semnan Provinces to the north, Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province to the east, Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Province to the south, and Lorestan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Isfahan Province is Isfahan city, with a population of over 5 million, making it one of the largest and most important cities in Iran. Isfahan is an ancient city with abundant cultural and historical heritage, including the Jameh Mosque of Isfahan, Fin Garden, and Naqsh-e Jahan Square.\nIsfahan Province has a diverse climate, with hot summers and moderate winters. It boasts numerous natural attractions such as the Central Desert, beautiful valleys, and waterfalls.\nThe economy of Isfahan Province is thriving due to the presence of heavy industries, agriculture, and handicrafts. Steel production, automotive manufacturing, petrochemicals, and agricultural products are among the important economic activities in this province.  Culturally, Isfahan Province has a rich history and culture. Isfahan is known as the cultural capital of Iran, attracting thousands of tourists from around the world each year to enjoy its cultural and historical beauties.</string>
    <string name="alborz_details" translatable="false">Alborz Province is one of the northern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 41,567 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Gilan Province to the north, Semnan Province to the east, Alborz and Tehran Provinces to the south, and Zanjan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Alborz Province is Karaj city, with a population of over 12 million, making it one of the most populous cities in Iran. Karaj is known as the industrial, commercial, and cultural center of Alborz Province.\nAlborz Province has a diverse climate, with cold winters and moderate summers. Its forests, rivers, and beautiful landscapes are among the natural attractions that attract many tourists.  Industry and agriculture are among the important economic activities in Alborz Province. Its agricultural productions include wheat, barley, apples, and potatoes. Additionally, industries such as food processing, textiles, and construction have developed in this province.\nCulturally, Alborz Province has a rich and diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="ilam_details" translatable="false">Ilam Province is one of the western provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 20,442 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Kermanshah Province to the north, Lorestan Province to the east, Khuzestan Province to the south, and Iraq to the west.\nThe capital of Ilam Province is Ilam city, with a population of over 632,000, making it one of the important cities in western Iran. This city has beautiful areas and numerous natural attractions that attract many tourists every year.\nIlam Province has a warm and dry climate, characterized by hot and sunny summers and moderate winters. It boasts areas with extraordinary beautiful landscapes, including Chavar County, Shahdeh Lor Valley, and Hoor Al-Azim Lagoon.\nVarious industries such as steel, oil, gas, and food industries operate in Ilam Province, contributing to the region\'s economy. Additionally, agriculture and animal husbandry have developed in this province, with diverse productions of agricultural and livestock products.\nCulturally, Ilam Province has a diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="bushehr_details" translatable="false">Bushehr Province is one of the southern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 36,482 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad, Fars, and Hormozgan Provinces to the north, the Persian Gulf to the east, and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province to the west.\nThe capital of Bushehr Province is Bushehr city, with a population of over 806,000, making it one of the major cities in southern Iran. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including beautiful beaches, shopping centers, and well-known ports such as Bandar Deylam and Bandar Kangan.\nBushehr Province has a warm and humid climate, characterized by hot summers and mild winters. It boasts numerous natural attractions, including Hormuz Island, Hengam National Park, and the mangrove forests of the Persian Gulf.\nThe oil and gas industries are major industries in Bushehr Province, significantly influencing the region\'s economy. Additionally, agriculture and fisheries have developed in this province and play a vital role in the regional economy.\nCulturally, Bushehr Province has a diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="tehran_details" translatable="false">Tehran Province is one of the central provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 18,641 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Alborz Province to the north, Semnan and Markazi Provinces to the east, Alborz and Qazvin Provinces to the south, and Qazvin Province to the west.\nThe capital of Tehran Province is Tehran city, with a population of over 13 million, making it the most populous city in Iran and one of the most populous cities in the world. This city is known as the economic, cultural, and political center of Iran and has numerous tourist attractions, including museums, Milad Tower, and Golestan Palace.\nTehran Province has a moderate climate with hot summers and mild winters. It boasts diverse natural landscapes and tourist attractions, including parks, gardens, and natural areas such as Shahrak-e Gharb and the Alborz Mountains.\nIndustry, marketing, and services are among the main economic sectors in Tehran Province, shaping the economy of this region. Additionally, agriculture and animal husbandry are practiced in some rural areas of this province.\nCulturally, Tehran Province has a rich history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="chahar_mahal_bakhtiari_details" translatable="false">Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Province is one of the southwestern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 16,528 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Isfahan and Lorestan Provinces to the north, Isfahan and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Provinces to the east, Kerman and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Provinces to the south, and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province to the west.\nThe capital of Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Province is Shahrekord city, with a population of over 842,000, making it the most important city in this province. This city is known as the cultural, economic, and commercial center of the province and has numerous tourist attractions, including Gonbad-e Alavi, Suriyan Cave, and the Hekmatan Hill in Shahrekord.\nChaharmahal and Bakhtiari Province has a moderate climate with cool summers and cold winters. Its natural landscapes include mountains, valleys, and beautiful rivers that attract many tourists every year.  Various industries including agriculture, animal husbandry, food industries, and handicrafts operate in Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Province, contributing to the development of the province\'s economy.\nCulturally, Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Province has a rich history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="south_khorasan_details" translatable="false">South Khorasan Province is one of the eastern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 92,436 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Razavi Khorasan Province to the north, Afghanistan to the east, Sistan and Baluchestan Province to the south, and North Khorasan Province to the west.\nThe capital of South Khorasan Province is Birjand city, with a population of over 783,000, making it the most important city in this province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including Nohbandan Castle, Shahdad Palace Museum, and Hamoun Lake.  South Khorasan Province has a dry and cold climate, with hot summers and cold winters. It boasts numerous natural attractions, including the Lut Desert, Ajichay Valley, and the beautiful mountains of Zahedan.\nVarious industries including agriculture, mining, and metallurgy operate in South Khorasan Province, contributing to the economy of this province. Additionally, animal husbandry and livestock breeding are practiced in some areas of this province.\nCulturally, South Khorasan Province has a diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="khorasan_razavi_details" translatable="false">Razavi Khorasan Province is one of the northeastern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 128,400 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Turkmenistan to the north, Afghanistan to the east, Semnan and South Khorasan Provinces to the south, and North Khorasan and Golestan Provinces to the west.\nThe capital of Razavi Khorasan Province is Mashhad city, with a population of over 3 million, making it the largest city in this province. This city is known as the religious and cultural center of Iran and hosts the holy shrine of Imam Reza (AS). It has numerous tourist attractions, including the Imam Reza Holy Shrine, museums, and local markets.\nRazavi Khorasan Province has a dry and cold climate, with hot summers and cold winters. It boasts beautiful natural landscapes, including the Khavaran Desert, Jon Waterfall valleys, and traditional villages like Nokhandan.\nEconomically, Razavi Khorasan Province has various industries including agriculture, mining, and handicrafts that contribute to the region\'s economic development. Tourism is also one of the most important sources of income in this province.</string>
    <string name="north_khorasan_details" translatable="false">North Khorasan Province is one of the northeastern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 28,421 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Turkmenistan to the north, Razavi Khorasan Province to the east, South Khorasan Province to the south, and Golestan and Mazandaran Provinces to the west.\nThe capital of North Khorasan Province is Bojnourd city, with a population of over 473,000, making it the most important city in this province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including Sultan Soltan Hamoun Hill, Bojnourd Old Camp Museum, and Marvavan Waterfall.\nNorth Khorasan Province has a warm and dry climate, with hot summers and cold winters. It boasts beautiful mountainous areas and natural landscapes, including the Esfarayen Mountains and Qara Qaray Ghaei Valley.\nVarious industries including agriculture, mining, and handicrafts operate in North Khorasan Province, contributing to the development of the province\'s economy. Additionally, animal husbandry and livestock breeding are practiced in some areas of this province.\nCulturally, North Khorasan Province has a diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="khozestan_details" translatable="false">Khuzestan Province is one of the southwestern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 63,231 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Lorestan, Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari, and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Provinces to the north, Bushehr Province to the east, the Persian Gulf to the south, and Iraq to the west.\nThe capital of Khuzestan Province is Ahvaz city, with a population of over 12 million, making it one of the most important cities in southern Iran. This city has a rich history, culture, and numerous tourist attractions, including Danube Park, Khuzestan National Museum, and Ahvaz Bridge.\nKhuzestan Province has a warm and dry climate, with hot summers and moderate winters. It boasts beautiful natural landscapes, including the Karun River, Hoor Al-Azim Marshlands, and the historic city of Susa.\nIndustries such as oil, gas, petrochemicals, steel, and agriculture are among the main industries in Khuzestan Province, contributing to its economy. Additionally, animal husbandry and fisheries are important activities in this province.\nCulturally, Khuzestan Province has a rich history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="zanjan_details" translatable="false">Zanjan Province is one of the northwestern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 22,488 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Gilan and Ardabil Provinces to the north, West Azerbaijan Province to the east, Hamadan Province to the south, and Kurdistan Province to the west. The capital of Zanjan Province is Zanjan city, with a population of over 416,000, making it the most important city in this province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including Zanjan Bazaar, Atashgah Tower, and Jameh Mosque of Zanjan. Zanjan Province has a cold, harsh climate, becoming cool in summers and cold in winters. It boasts beautiful mountainous areas and natural landscapes, including the village of Abhar, Gorgan Valley, and the Saint Stephanos Church. Various industries including agriculture, textiles, and handicrafts operate in Zanjan Province, contributing to its economic development. Additionally, animal husbandry and horticulture are important economic activities in this province. Culturally, Zanjan Province has a diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="semnan_details" translatable="false">Semnan Province is one of the eastern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 96,327 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Mazandaran Province to the north, North Khorasan Province to the east, Semnan Province to the south, and Qazvin and Tehran Provinces to the west.\nThe capital of Semnan Province is Semnan city, with a population of over 270,000, making it the most important city in this province. This city has various tourist attractions, including Atashgah Tower, Roodbarak Waterfall, and Sarakhs Spring.\nSemnan Province has a semi-arid and cold climate, with hot summers and cold winters. Its natural landscapes include mountains, valleys, and beautiful deserts that attract many tourists every year.\nVarious industries including agriculture, textiles, and food production operate in Semnan Province, contributing to its economic development. Additionally, animal husbandry and livestock breeding are practiced in some areas of this province.\nCulturally, Semnan Province has a diverse history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="sistan_baluchistan_details" translatable="false">Sistan and Baluchestan Province is one of the southeastern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 187,422 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Razavi Khorasan and South Khorasan Provinces to the north, Afghanistan and Pakistan to the east, Hormozgan Province and the Gulf of Oman to the south, and Sistan and Baluchestan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Sistan and Baluchestan Province is Zahedan city, with a population of over 615,000, making it the most important city in this province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including Shahzadeh Qajar Tower, Deh Faras Fortress, and Shahdad Garden.\nSistan and Baluchestan Province has a dry and hot climate, becoming extremely hot in summers and moderate in winters. It boasts beautiful natural landscapes, including the Lut Desert, the islands of Hormuz, and Hamoun Lakes.\nVarious industries including agriculture, mining, and handicrafts operate in Sistan and Baluchestan Province, contributing to its economic development. Additionally, animal husbandry and livestock breeding are practiced in some areas of this province.\nCulturally, Sistan and Baluchestan Province has a rich history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="fars_details" translatable="false">Fars Province is one of the southern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 153,000 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It shares borders with Isfahan and Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Provinces to the north, Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province to the east, the Persian Gulf to the south, and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad and Bushehr Provinces to the west.\nThe capital of Fars Province is Shiraz city, with a population of over 1,830,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including Eram Garden, Pasargadae, and Nasir al-Mulk Mosque.\nFars Province has a warm and dry climate, with extremely hot summers and moderate winters. It boasts mountainous regions, plains, and beautiful natural landscapes, including the Marvdasht Plain, Eqleed County, and the Zagros Mountains.\nVarious industries including agriculture, oil and gas, petrochemicals, and handicrafts operate in Fars Province, contributing to its economic development. Additionally, animal husbandry and horticulture are important economic activities in some areas of this province.\nCulturally, Fars Province has a rich history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="qazvin_details" translatable="false">Qazvin Province is one of the northern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 15,400 square kilometers, making it one of the smaller provinces in the country. It borders Mazandaran Province to the north, Tehran Province to the east, Alborz Province to the south, and Hamadan and Zanjan Provinces to the west.\nThe capital of Qazvin Province is Qazvin city, with a population of over 125,000, making it the most important city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including historical gates, Sultanieh Tower, and Jameh Mosque of Qazvin.\nQazvin Province has a moderate and cool climate, with cool summers and cold winters. It boasts beautiful and diverse natural landscapes, including the Hir Forests, Siah Valley, and mountainous villages.\nVarious industries including agriculture, industrial production, and handicrafts operate in Qazvin Province, contributing to its economic development. Additionally, animal husbandry and horticulture are important economic activities in this province.\nCulturally, Qazvin Province has a rich history and culture and hosts numerous historical and cultural attractions that attract many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="qom_details" translatable="false">Qom Province is one of the central provinces of Iran, covering an area of approximately 11,831 square kilometers, making it one of the smaller provinces in the country. It borders Tehran and Alborz Provinces to the north, Semnan Province to the east, Markazi Province to the south, and Qazvin Province to the west.\nThe capital of Qom Province is the city of Qom, with a population of over 1,260,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. Qom is one of the major religious centers in Iran and has many pilgrimage sites, including the holy shrines of Hazrat Masoumeh (SA).\nQom Province has a semi-arid and hot climate, with extremely hot summers and moderate winters. It boasts beautiful natural landscapes, including natural valleys, the Central Desert, and white mountains.\nThe economy of Qom Province relies mainly on agricultural activities such as farming and animal husbandry, as well as handicrafts. Additionally, industrial production and services contribute to the economic development of this region.</string>
    <string name="kurdistan_datails" translatable="false">Kurdistan Province is one of the northwest provinces of Iran, with its center located in the city of Sanandaj. It borders West Azerbaijan Province to the north, Zanjan Province to the northeast, Hamadan Province to the southeast, Lorestan Province to the south, and Iraq to the west. Due to its geographical location, being mountainous and hilly, the climate of the province is moderate and cold. Kurdistan Province boasts beautiful tourist attractions such as the Shirinabad and Marivan valleys, lush oak forests, and numerous historical sites.\nVarious ethnic groups including Kurds, Lurs, Persians, and Turks inhabit this province. The official and common language of Kurdistan Province is Kurdish, but parts of the population also speak Persian and Turkish. The economy of this province is mainly based on agriculture, animal husbandry, and handicrafts. Additionally, mining industries play a significant role in this region, with ongoing extraction of minerals such as coal and iron.\nKurdistan Province is home to reputable universities and educational centers that contribute to the advancement of knowledge and culture within the society. Moreover, the rich natural resources and tourism potentials of this province have attracted both domestic and international tourists to the area.</string>
    <string name="kerman_details" translatable="false">Kerman Province is one of the largest and most important provinces in Iran, located in the eastern part of the country, covering an area of over 286,641 square kilometers. It is bordered by Yazd and Sistan and Baluchestan Provinces to the north, Hormozgan and Kermanshah Provinces to the east, Hormozgan and Bushehr Provinces to the south, and Fars and Yazd Provinces to the west.\nThe capital of Kerman Province is the city of Kerman, with a population of over 980,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has a rich history and culture and numerous tourist attractions, including Fin Garden, Ganjali Khan Complex, and Kerman Historical Bazaar.\nKerman Province has a diverse climate, with hot and dry conditions in the southern regions and moderate climates in the northern areas. It boasts diverse natural landscapes, including the Lut Desert, Jiroft Plain, and Hamun River.\nThe economy of Kerman Province relies on mining and mineral industries, agriculture, and handicrafts. Additionally, industries related to agricultural products such as livestock farming, animal feed production, and agricultural packaging thrive in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="kermanshah_details" translatable="false">Kermanshah Province is one of the western provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 24,620 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It borders Kurdistan and Zanjan Provinces to the north, Hamadan Province to the east, Lorestan and Khuzestan Provinces to the south, and Iraq to the west.\nThe capital of Kermanshah Province is Kermanshah city, with a population of over 880,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including the Takht-e Jamshid Hills, Zeytun Waterfall, and the British Museum.\nKermanshah Province has a semi-arid and hot climate, with extremely hot summers and moderate winters. It boasts diverse nature, including mountains, valleys, and beautiful hills.\nThe economy of Kermanshah Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, mining industries, and handicrafts. Additionally, construction industries and industrial production also take place in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="kohgiloyeh_and_boyerahmad_details" translatable="false">Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province is one of the southern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 15,526 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders Fars Province to the north, Kerman Province to the east, Bushehr Province and Oman to the south, and Lorestan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province is Yasuj city, with a population of over 110,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has various tourist attractions, including the warm springs of Vali-e Asr, beautiful natural valleys, and Rudkhan Castle.\nKohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province has a moderate climate in coastal areas and a cold climate in mountainous regions. It boasts beautiful and mesmerizing natural landscapes, including mountains, forests, and deep valleys.\nThe economy of Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, animal husbandry, and handicrafts. Additionally, industrial and mining productions exist in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="golestan_details" translatable="false">Golestan Province is one of the northeastern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 20,510 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders the Caspian Sea to the north, North Khorasan Province to the east, Mazandaran Province to the south, and Gilan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Golestan Province is Gorgan city, with a population of over 710,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has various tourist attractions, including the Golestan Ethnographic Museum, Karim Khan Artistic Zone, and the Caspian Sea coast.\nGolestan Province has a semi-arid and moderate climate, with hot summers and moderate winters. It boasts beautiful and diverse natural landscapes, including forests, lakes, and beautiful pastures.\nThe economy of Golestan Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, fisheries, and handicrafts. Additionally, industrial and mining productions exist in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="gilan_details" translatable="false">Gilan Province is one of the northern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 14,000 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders the Caspian Sea to the north, Mazandaran Province to the east, Qazvin and Alborz Provinces to the south, and East Azerbaijan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Gilan Province is Rasht city, with a population of over 590,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including Shahid Rajaee National Botanical Garden, the largest water park in Iran, and the Museum of Contemporary Arts.\nGilan Province has a moderate and humid climate, with cool summers and mild winters. It boasts pristine and beautiful nature, including forests, lakes, and lush green mountains.\nThe economy of Gilan Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, fisheries, and handicrafts. Additionally, tourism is one of the most important sources of income in this province, attracting many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="lorestan_details" translatable="false">Lorestan Province is one of the western provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 28,597 square kilometers, making it one of the largest provinces in the country. It borders Kermanshah and Hamadan Provinces to the north, Hamadan Province to the east, Khuzestan and Kohgiluyeh and Boyer-Ahmad Provinces to the south, and Kurdistan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Lorestan Province is Khorramabad city, with a population of over 475,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has various tourist attractions, including the mineral springs of Golestan, the Black and White Valleys, and pleasant hills.\nLorestan Province has a semi-arid and mountainous climate, with hot summers and cold winters. It boasts beautiful and unique natural landscapes, including mountains, valleys, and charming waterfalls.\nThe economy of Lorestan Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, animal husbandry, and handicrafts. Additionally, construction and mining industries exist in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="mazandaran_details" translatable="false">Mazandaran Province is one of the northern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 17,948 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders the Caspian Sea to the north, Golestan Province to the east, Semnan and Tehran Provinces to the south, and Alborz Province to the west.\nThe capital of Mazandaran Province is Sari city, with a population of over 600,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including hiking in the forests of Hir, the bustling market of Rudkhan Castle, and the beautiful beach of Kiashahr.\nMazandaran Province has a humid and moderate climate, with cool summers and mild winters. It boasts abundant and beautiful natural landscapes, including lush forests, stunning coastlines, and rivers.\nThe economy of Mazandaran Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, fisheries, and tourism. Additionally, processing industries, handicrafts, and cottage industries are also active in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="markazi_details" translatable="false">Markazi Province is one of the central provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 29,232 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders Qazvin and Alborz Provinces to the north, Semnan Province to the east, Isfahan Province to the south, and Hamadan Province to the west.\nThe capital of Markazi Province is Arak city, with a population of over 510,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has various tourist attractions, including Azadi Tower, Central Museum, and Central Park.\nMarkazi Province has a semi-arid and moderate climate, with hot summers and cold winters. It boasts beautiful and diverse natural landscapes, including mountains, plains, and beautiful rivers.\nThe economy of Markazi Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, animal husbandry, and processing industries. Additionally, handicrafts and construction industry are also thriving in this province, contributing to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="hormozgan_details" translatable="false">Hormozgan Province is one of the southern provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 17,552 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders Fars Province to the north, Kerman Province to the east, the Persian Gulf to the south, and Bushehr Province to the west.\nThe capital of Hormozgan Province is Bandar Abbas city, with a population of over 725,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including the islands of Qeshm and Hormuz, Farahan Castle, and the beautiful beaches of Hormuz Island.\nHormozgan Province has a warm and dry climate, with very hot summers and mild to warm winters. It boasts very beautiful and diverse natural landscapes, including stunning coastlines, tropical islands, and bustling ports.\nThe economy of Hormozgan Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, fisheries, and maritime industries. Additionally, tourism is one of the most important sources of income in this province, attracting many tourists annually.</string>
    <string name="hamedan_details" translatable="false">Hamadan Province is one of the western provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 23,343 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders Zanjan Province to the north, Markazi and Qom Provinces to the east, Lorestan and Chaharmahal and Bakhtiari Provinces to the south, and Kermanshah Province to the west.\nThe capital of Hamadan Province is Hamadan city, with a population of over 735,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has various tourist attractions, including the Alavi Dome, Toghrul Tower, and hot springs.\nHamadan Province has a semi-arid and cold climate, with hot summers and cold winters. It boasts beautiful and diverse natural landscapes, including mountains, valleys, and hot springs.\nThe economy of Hamadan Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, animal husbandry, and processing industries. Additionally, there are various mines in this province, including coal, iron, and salt mines, which contribute to its economic development.</string>
    <string name="yazd_details" translatable="false">Yazd Province is one of the central provinces of Iran, covering an area of over 67,991 square kilometers, making it one of the larger provinces in the country. It borders Semnan and South Khorasan Provinces to the north, Razavi Khorasan Province to the east, Kerman Province to the south, and Fars Province to the west.\nThe capital of Yazd Province is Yazd city, with a population of over 650,000, making it the largest city and capital of the province. This city has numerous tourist attractions, including the Bagh-e Eram, Dolat Abad Garden, and Chekoh Waterfall.\nYazd Province has a semi-arid and warm climate, with very hot summers and moderate to cold winters. It boasts beautiful and diverse natural landscapes, including deserts, plains, and stunning mountains.\nThe economy of Yazd Province relies mainly on agricultural activities, animal husbandry, and handicrafts. Additionally, tourism is one of the most important sources of income in this province, attracting many tourists annually.</string>

    <!-- East Azarbaijan -->
    <string name="azar_shahr" translatable="false">Azar Shahr</string>
    <string name="osku" translatable="false">Osko</string>
    <string name="ahar" translatable="false">Ahar</string>
    <string name="bostan_abad" translatable="false">Bostan Abad</string>
    <string name="jolfa" translatable="false">Jolfa</string>
    <string name="charavimaq" translatable="false">Charavimaq</string>
    <string name="khoda_afarin" translatable="false">Khoda Afarin</string>
    <string name="sarab" translatable="false">Sarab</string>
    <string name="shabestar" translatable="false">Shabestar</string>
    <string name="ajab_shir" translatable="false">Ajab Shir</string>
    <string name="kalibar" translatable="false">Kalibar</string>
    <string name="maragheh" translatable="false">Maragheh</string>
    <string name="marand" translatable="false">Marand</string>
    <string name="malekan" translatable="false">Malekan</string>
    <string name="miyaneh" translatable="false">Miyaneh</string>
    <string name="varzeqan" translatable="false">Varzeqan</string>
    <string name="heris" translatable="false">Heris</string>
    <string name="hashtrud" translatable="false">Hashtrud</string>
    <string name="hurand" translatable="false">Hurand</string>
    <string name="tabriz" translatable="false">Tabriz</string>
    <string name="bonab" translatable="false">Bonab</string>

    <!-- West Azarbaijan -->
    <string name="urmia" translatable="false">Urmia</string>
    <string name="oshnavieh" translatable="false">Oshnavieh</string>
    <string name="bokan" translatable="false">Bokan</string>
    <string name="piranshahr" translatable="false">Piranshahr</string>
    <string name="takab" translatable="false">Takab</string>
    <string name="khoy" translatable="false">Khoy</string>
    <string name="chaldoran" translatable="false">Chaldoran</string>
    <string name="chaypareh" translatable="false">Chaypareh</string>
    <string name="shut" translatable="false">Shut</string>
    <string name="poldasht" translatable="false">Poldasht</string>
    <string name="sardasht" translatable="false">Sardasht</string>
    <string name="salmas" translatable="false">Salmas</string>
    <string name="shahin_dej" translatable="false">Shahin Dej</string>
    <string name="maku" translatable="false">Maku</string>
    <string name="mahabad" translatable="false">Mahabad</string>
    <string name="miandoab" translatable="false">Miandoab</string>
    <string name="naqadeh" translatable="false">Naqadeh</string>
    <string name="chaharborj" translatable="false">Chaharborj</string>
    <string name="baroq" translatable="false">Baroq</string>


    <!-- Ardabil -->
    <string name="aslan_duz" translatable="false">Aslan Duz</string>
    <string name="ongut" translatable="false">Ongut</string>
    <string name="bileh_savar" translatable="false">Bileh Savar</string>
    <string name="parsabad" translatable="false">Parsabad</string>
    <string name="khalkhal" translatable="false">Khalkhal</string>
    <string name="sareyn" translatable="false">Sareyn</string>
    <string name="kowsar" translatable="false">Kowsar</string>
    <string name="germi" translatable="false">Germi</string>
    <string name="meshginshahr" translatable="false">Meshginshahr</string>
    <string name="namin" translatable="false">Namin</string>
    <string name="nir" translatable="false">Nir</string>

    <!-- Esfahan -->
    <string name="aran_and_bidgol" translatable="false">Aran And Bidgol</string>
    <string name="ardestan" translatable="false">Ardestan</string>
    <string name="borkhar" translatable="false">Borkhar</string>
    <string name="bueen_and_miyandasht" translatable="false">Bueen And Miyandasht</string>
    <string name="tiran_and_korun" translatable="false">Tiran And Korun</string>
    <string name="chadegan" translatable="false">Chadegan</string>
    <string name="khomeyni_shahr" translatable="false">Khomeyni Shahr</string>
    <string name="khansar" translatable="false">Khansar</string>
    <string name="khur_and_biabanak" translatable="false">Khur and Biabanak</string>
    <string name="semirom" translatable="false">Semirom</string>
    <string name="shahin_Shahr_and_meymeh" translatable="false">Shahin Shahr and Meymeh</string>
    <string name="shahreza" translatable="false">Shahreza</string>
    <string name="dehaqan" translatable="false">Dehaqan</string>
    <string name="faridan" translatable="false">Faridan</string>
    <string name="fereydun_shahr" translatable="false">Fereydun Shahr</string>
    <string name="falavarjan" translatable="false">Falavarjan</string>
    <string name="kashan" translatable="false">Kashan</string>
    <string name="golpayegan" translatable="false">Golpayegan</string>
    <string name="lenjan" translatable="false">Lenjan</string>
    <string name="mobarakeh" translatable="false">Mobarakeh</string>
    <string name="naeen" translatable="false">Naeen</string>
    <string name="najafabad" translatable="false">Najafabad</string>
    <string name="natanz" translatable="false">Natanz</string>

    <!-- Alborz -->
    <string name="eshtehard" translatable="false">Eshtehard</string>
    <string name="charbagh" translatable="false">Charbagh</string>
    <string name="savojbolagh" translatable="false">Savojbolagh</string>
    <string name="taleqan" translatable="false">Taleqan</string>
    <string name="fardis" translatable="false">Fardis</string>
    <string name="karaj" translatable="false">Karaj</string>
    <string name="nazarabad" translatable="false">Nazarabad</string>


    <!-- Ilam -->
    <string name="abdanan" translatable="false">Abdanan</string>
    <string name="eyvan" translatable="false">Eyvan</string>
    <string name="badreh" translatable="false">Badreh</string>
    <string name="chardavol" translatable="false">Chardavol</string>
    <string name="chovar" translatable="false">Chovar</string>
    <string name="darreh_shahr" translatable="false">Darreh Shahr</string>
    <string name="dehloran" translatable="false">Dehloran</string>
    <string name="sirvan" translatable="false">Sirvan</string>
    <string name="malekshahi" translatable="false">Malekshahi</string>
    <string name="mehran" translatable="false">Mehran</string>
    <string name="holeylan" translatable="false">Holeylan</string>

    <!-- Bushehr -->
    <string name="tangestan" translatable="false">Tangestan</string>
    <string name="jam" translatable="false">Jam</string>
    <string name="dashtestan" translatable="false">Dashtestan</string>
    <string name="dashti" translatable="false">Dashti</string>
    <string name="dayyer" translatable="false">Dayyer</string>
    <string name="deylam" translatable="false">Deylam</string>
    <string name="asaluyeh" translatable="false">Asaluyeh</string>
    <string name="kangan" translatable="false">Kangan</string>
    <string name="ganaveh" translatable="false">Ganaveh</string>

    <!-- Tehran -->
    <string name="eslamShahr" translatable="false">EslamShahr</string>
    <string name="baharestan" translatable="false">Baharestan</string>
    <string name="pakdasht" translatable="false">Pakdasht</string>
    <string name="pardis" translatable="false">Pardis</string>
    <string name="pishva" translatable="false">Pishva</string>
    <string name="damavand" translatable="false">Damavand</string>
    <string name="robat_karim" translatable="false">Robat Karim</string>
    <string name="rey" translatable="false">Rey</string>
    <string name="shemiranat" translatable="false">Shemiranat</string>
    <string name="shahriar" translatable="false">Shahriar</string>
    <string name="firuzkuh" translatable="false">Firuzkuh</string>
    <string name="qods" translatable="false">Qods</string>
    <string name="qarchak" translatable="false">Qarchak</string>
    <string name="malard" translatable="false">Malard</string>
    <string name="varamin" translatable="false">Varamin</string>

    <!-- Chahar Mahal Bakhtiari -->
    <string name="ardal" translatable="false">Ardal</string>
    <string name="borujen" translatable="false">Borujen</string>
    <string name="ben" translatable="false">Ben</string>
    <string name="khanmirza" translatable="false">Khanmirza</string>
    <string name="saman" translatable="false">Saman</string>
    <string name="shahrekord" translatable="false">Shahrekord</string>
    <string name="farsan" translatable="false">Farsan</string>
    <string name="farokhshahr" translatable="false">Farokhshahr</string>
    <string name="falard" translatable="false">Falard</string>
    <string name="kuhrang" translatable="false">Kuhrang</string>
    <string name="kiar" translatable="false">Kiar</string>
    <string name="lordegan" translatable="false">Lordegan</string>

    <!-- South Khorasna -->
    <string name="boshruyeh" translatable="false">Boshruyeh</string>
    <string name="birjand" translatable="false">Birjand</string>
    <string name="khosf" translatable="false">Khosf</string>
    <string name="darmian" translatable="false">Darmian</string>
    <string name="zirkuh" translatable="false">Zirkuh</string>
    <string name="sarayan" translatable="false">Sarayan</string>
    <string name="sarbisheh" translatable="false">Sarbisheh</string>
    <string name="tabas" translatable="false">Tabas</string>
    <string name="ferdows" translatable="false">Ferdows</string>
    <string name="qaen" translatable="false">Qaen</string>
    <string name="nehbandan" translatable="false">Nehbandan</string>

    <!-- Khorasan Razavi  -->
    <string name="bakharz" translatable="false">Bakharz</string>
    <string name="bajestan" translatable="false">Bajestan</string>
    <string name="bardaskan" translatable="false">Bardaskan</string>
    <string name="taybad" translatable="false">Taybad</string>
    <string name="torbat_e_jam" translatable="false">Torbat-e-Jam</string>
    <string name="torbat_e_heydariyeh" translatable="false">Torbat-e-Heydariyeh</string>
    <string name="joghatay" translatable="false">Joghatay</string>
    <string name="joveyn" translatable="false">Joveyn</string>
    <string name="chenaran" translatable="false">Chenaran</string>
    <string name="khalil_abad" translatable="false">Khalil Abad</string>
    <string name="khaf" translatable="false">Khaf</string>
    <string name="khoshab" translatable="false">Khoshab</string>
    <string name="davarzan" translatable="false">Davarzan</string>
    <string name="dargaz" translatable="false">Dargaz</string>
    <string name="roshtkhar" translatable="false">Roshtkhar</string>
    <string name="zaveh" translatable="false">Zaveh</string>
    <string name="zeberkhan" translatable="false">Zeberkhan</string>
    <string name="sabzevar" translatable="false">Sabzevar</string>
    <string name="sarakhs" translatable="false">Sarakhs</string>
    <string name="sheshtamad" translatable="false">Sheshtamad</string>
    <string name="salehabad" translatable="false">Salehabad</string>
    <string name="torghabe_shandiz" translatable="false">Torghabe Shandiz</string>
    <string name="fariman" translatable="false">Fariman</string>
    <string name="firuzeh" translatable="false">Firuzeh</string>
    <string name="quchan" translatable="false">Quchan</string>
    <string name="kashmar" translatable="false">Kashmar</string>
    <string name="kalat" translatable="false">Kalat</string>
    <string name="kuhsorkh" translatable="false">Kuhsorkh</string>
    <string name="golbahar" translatable="false">Golbahar</string>
    <string name="gonabad" translatable="false">Gonabad</string>
    <string name="mashhad" translatable="false">Mashhad</string>
    <string name="mahvelat" translatable="false">Mahvelat</string>
    <string name="miyan_jolgeh" translatable="false">Miyan Jolgeh</string>
    <string name="neyshabur" translatable="false">Neyshabur</string>

    <!-- North Khorasna -->
    <string name="esfarayen" translatable="false">Esfarayen</string>
    <string name="bojnurd" translatable="false">Bojnurd</string>
    <string name="jajarm" translatable="false">Jajarm</string>
    <string name="raz_and_jargalan" translatable="false">Raz and Jargalan</string>
    <string name="shirvan" translatable="false">Shirvan</string>
    <string name="faruj" translatable="false">Faruj</string>
    <string name="garmeh" translatable="false">Garmeh</string>
    <string name="maneh_and_samalqan" translatable="false">Maneh and Samalqan</string>

    <!--  Khozestan  -->
    <string name="abadan" translatable="false">Abadan</string>
    <string name="omidiyeh" translatable="false">Omidiyeh</string>
    <string name="andika" translatable="false">Andika</string>
    <string name="andimeshk" translatable="false">Andimeshk</string>
    <string name="ahvaz" translatable="false">Ahvaz</string>
    <string name="izeh" translatable="false">Izeh</string>
    <string name="baghmalek" translatable="false">Baghmalek</string>
    <string name="bavi" translatable="false">Bavi</string>
    <string name="behbahan" translatable="false">Behbahan</string>
    <string name="khorramshahr" translatable="false">Khorramshahr</string>
    <string name="dezpart" translatable="false">Dezpart</string>
    <string name="dezful" translatable="false">Dezful</string>
    <string name="dasht_e_azadegan" translatable="false">Dasht Azadegan</string>
    <string name="ramshir" translatable="false">Ramshir</string>
    <string name="ramhormoz" translatable="false">Ramhormoz</string>
    <string name="shadegan" translatable="false">Shadegan</string>
    <string name="shush" translatable="false">Shush</string>
    <string name="shushtar" translatable="false">Shushtar</string>
    <string name="gotvand" translatable="false">Gotvand</string>
    <string name="lally" translatable="false">Lally</string>
    <string name="mahshahr" translatable="false">Mahshahr</string>
    <string name="masjed_soleyman" translatable="false">Masjed Soleyman</string>
    <string name="haftgel" translatable="false">Haftgel</string>
    <string name="hendijan" translatable="false">Hendijan</string>
    <string name="hoveyzeh" translatable="false">Hoveyzeh</string>

    <!--  Zanjan  -->
    <string name="abhar" translatable="false">Abhar</string>
    <string name="ijrud" translatable="false">Ijrud</string>
    <string name="khodabandeh" translatable="false">Khodabandeh</string>
    <string name="khorramdarreh" translatable="false">Khorramdarreh</string>
    <string name="soltaniyeh" translatable="false">Soltaniyeh</string>
    <string name="tarom" translatable="false">Tarom</string>
    <string name="mahneshan" translatable="false">Mahneshan</string>


    <!--  Semnan  -->
    <string name="ardan" translatable="false">Ardan</string>
    <string name="damghan" translatable="false">Damghan</string>
    <string name="sorkheh" translatable="false">Sorkheh</string>
    <string name="shahrood" translatable="false">Shahrood</string>
    <string name="garmsar" translatable="false">Garmsar</string>
    <string name="mehdishahr" translatable="false">Mehdishahr</string>
    <string name="maime" translatable="false">Maime</string>


    <!--  sistan Balouchsestan  -->
    <string name="iranshahr" translatable="false">Iranshahr</string>
    <string name="bampur" translatable="false">Bampur</string>
    <string name="taftan" translatable="false">Taftan</string>
    <string name="chah_bahar" translatable="false">Chah Bahar</string>
    <string name="khash" translatable="false">Khash</string>
    <string name="dashtiari" translatable="false">Dashtiari</string>
    <string name="dalgan" translatable="false">Dalgan</string>
    <string name="rask" translatable="false">Rask</string>
    <string name="zabol" translatable="false">Zabol</string>
    <string name="zahedan" translatable="false">Zahedan</string>
    <string name="zarabad" translatable="false">Zarabad</string>
    <string name="zahak" translatable="false">Zahak</string>
    <string name="sarbaz" translatable="false">Sarbaz</string>
    <string name="sib_and_suran" translatable="false">Sib and Suran</string>
    <string name="fanuj" translatable="false">Fanuj</string>
    <string name="qasreqand" translatable="false">Qasreqand</string>
    <string name="konarak" translatable="false">Konarak</string>
    <string name="golshan" translatable="false">Golshan</string>
    <string name="lashar" translatable="false">Lashar</string>
    <string name="mehrestan" translatable="false">Mehrestan</string>
    <string name="mirjaveh" translatable="false">Mirjaveh</string>
    <string name="nikshahr" translatable="false">Nikshahr</string>
    <string name="nimruz" translatable="false">Nimruz</string>
    <string name="hamoun" translatable="false">Hamoun</string>
    <string name="hirmand" translatable="false">Hirmand</string>

    <!--  Fars  -->
    <string name="abade" translatable="false">Abade</string>
    <string name="arsenjan" translatable="false">Arsenjan</string>
    <string name="estahban" translatable="false">Estahban</string>
    <string name="eqlid" translatable="false">Eqlid</string>
    <string name="evaz" translatable="false">Evaz</string>
    <string name="bakhtegan" translatable="false">Bakhtegan</string>
    <string name="bavanat" translatable="false">Bavana</string>
    <string name="beyza" translatable="false">Beyza</string>
    <string name="pasargad" translatable="false">pasargad</string>
    <string name="joyom" translatable="false">Joyom</string>
    <string name="jahrom" translatable="false">Jahrom</string>
    <string name="kharameh" translatable="false">Kharameh</string>
    <string name="khorrambid" translatable="false">Khorrambid</string>
    <string name="khafr" translatable="false">Khafr</string>
    <string name="darab" translatable="false">Darab</string>
    <string name="rostam" translatable="false">Rostam</string>
    <string name="zarqan" translatable="false">Zarqan</string>
    <string name="zarrin_dasht" translatable="false">Zarrin Dasht</string>
    <string name="sepidan" translatable="false">Sepidan</string>
    <string name="sarchehan" translatable="false">Sarchehan</string>
    <string name="sarvestan" translatable="false">Sarvestan</string>
    <string name="shiraz" translatable="false">Shiraz</string>
    <string name="farashband" translatable="false">Farashband</string>
    <string name="fasa" translatable="false">Fasa</string>
    <string name="firuzabad" translatable="false">Firuzabad</string>
    <string name="qir_and_karzin" translatable="false">Qir and Karzin</string>
    <string name="kazerun" translatable="false">Kazerun</string>
    <string name="kavar" translatable="false">Kavar</string>
    <string name="kuhchenar" translatable="false">Kuhchenar</string>
    <string name="gerash" translatable="false">Gerash</string>
    <string name="larestan" translatable="false">Larestan</string>
    <string name="lamerd" translatable="false">Lamerd</string>
    <string name="marvdasht" translatable="false">Marvdasht</string>
    <string name="mamasani" translatable="false">Mamasani</string>
    <string name="mohr" translatable="false">Mohr</string>
    <string name="neyriz" translatable="false">Nayriz</string>

    <!--  qazvin  -->
    <string name="abeyk" translatable="false">Abeyk</string>
    <string name="avaj" translatable="false">Avaj</string>
    <string name="bueenzahra" translatable="false">Bueenzahra</string>
    <string name="takestan" translatable="false">Takestan</string>

    <!--  qom  -->
    <string name="jafariyeh" translatable="false">Jafariyeh</string>
    <string name="kahak" translatable="false">Kahak</string>

    <!--  kurdestan  -->
    <string name="baneh" translatable="false">Baneh</string>
    <string name="bijar" translatable="false">Bijar</string>
    <string name="dehgolan" translatable="false">Dehgolan</string>
    <string name="divandarreh" translatable="false">Divandarreh</string>
    <string name="sarvabad" translatable="false">Sarvabad</string>
    <string name="qorveh" translatable="false">Qorveh</string>
    <string name="kamyaran" translatable="false">Kamyaran</string>
    <string name="marivan" translatable="false">Marivan</string>

    <!--  Kerman  -->
    <string name="orzueeyeh" translatable="false">Orzueeyeh</string>
    <string name="anar" translatable="false">Anar</string>
    <string name="baft" translatable="false">Baft</string>
    <string name="bardsir" translatable="false">Bardsir</string>
    <string name="bam" translatable="false">Bam</string>
    <string name="jaz_murian" translatable="false">Jaz Murian</string>
    <string name="jiroft" translatable="false">Jiroft</string>
    <string name="rabor" translatable="false">Rabor</string>
    <string name="rafsanjan" translatable="false">Rafsanjan</string>
    <string name="rudbar_jonubi" translatable="false">Rudbar Jonubi</string>
    <string name="rigan" translatable="false">Rigan</string>
    <string name="zarand" translatable="false">Zarand</string>
    <string name="sirjan" translatable="false">Sirjan</string>
    <string name="shahr_babak" translatable="false">Shahr Babak</string>
    <string name="anbarabad" translatable="false">Anbarabad</string>
    <string name="faryab" translatable="false">Faryab</string>
    <string name="fahraj" translatable="false">Fahraj</string>
    <string name="qalehganj" translatable="false">Qalehganj</string>
    <string name="kuhbanan" translatable="false">Kuhbanan</string>
    <string name="kahnuj" translatable="false">Kahnuj</string>
    <string name="ganbaki" translatable="false">Gonbaki</string>
    <string name="manujan" translatable="false">Manujan</string>
    <string name="narmashir" translatable="false">Narmashir</string>

    <!--  Kermanshah  -->
    <string name="eslamabad_gharb" translatable="false">Eslamabad Gharb</string>
    <string name="paveh" translatable="false">Paveh</string>
    <string name="salas_babajani" translatable="false">Salas Babajani</string>
    <string name="javanrud" translatable="false">Javanrud</string>
    <string name="dalahu" translatable="false">Dalahu</string>
    <string name="ravansar" translatable="false">Ravansar</string>
    <string name="sarpol_zahab" translatable="false">Sarpol Zahab</string>
    <string name="sonqor" translatable="false">Sonqor</string>
    <string name="sahneh" translatable="false">Sahneh</string>
    <string name="gasr_shirin" translatable="false">Gasr Shirin</string>
    <string name="kangavar" translatable="false">Kangavar</string>
    <string name="gilanegharb" translatable="false">Gilanegharb</string>
    <string name="harsin" translatable="false">Harsin</string>

    <!--  kohgoloyeh and boyorahmad  -->
    <string name="basht" translatable="false">Basht</string>
    <string name="boyer_ahmad" translatable="false">Boyer Ahmad</string>
    <string name="bahmai" translatable="false">Bahmai</string>
    <string name="choram" translatable="false">Choram</string>
    <string name="dena" translatable="false">Dena</string>
    <string name="kohgiluyeh" translatable="false">Kohgiluyeh</string>
    <string name="gachsaran" translatable="false">Gachsaran</string>
    <string name="landeh" translatable="false">Landeh</string>
    <string name="maregoon" translatable="false">Maregoon</string>

    <!--  golestan  -->
    <string name="azadshahr" translatable="false">Azadshahr</string>
    <string name="aqqala" translatable="false">Aqqala</string>
    <string name="bandar_gaz" translatable="false">Bandar Gaz</string>
    <string name="torkaman" translatable="false">Torkaman</string>
    <string name="ramiyan" translatable="false">Ramiyan</string>
    <string name="ali_abad" translatable="false">Ali Abad</string>
    <string name="kordkuy" translatable="false">Kordkuy</string>
    <string name="kalaleh" translatable="false">Kalaleh</string>
    <string name="galikesh" translatable="false">Galikesh</string>
    <string name="gorgan" translatable="false">Gorgan</string>
    <string name="gomishan" translatable="false">Gomishan</string>
    <string name="gonbad_kavus" translatable="false">Gonbad Kavus</string>
    <string name="marave_tappeh" translatable="false">Maraveh Tappeh</string>
    <string name="minodasht" translatable="false">Minodasht</string>

    <!--  gilan  -->
    <string name="astara" translatable="false">Astara</string>
    <string name="astaneh_ashrafiyeh" translatable="false">Astaneh Ashrafiyeh</string>
    <string name="amlash" translatable="false">Amlash</string>
    <string name="bandar_anzali" translatable="false">Bandar Anzali</string>
    <string name="talesh" translatable="false">Talesh</string>
    <string name="khomam" translatable="false">Khomam</string>
    <string name="rasht" translatable="false">Rasht</string>
    <string name="rezvanshahr" translatable="false">Rezvanshahr</string>
    <string name="rudbar" translatable="false">Rudbar</string>
    <string name="rudsar" translatable="false">Rudsar</string>
    <string name="siahkal" translatable="false">Siahkal</string>
    <string name="shaft" translatable="false">Shaft</string>
    <string name="someh_sara" translatable="false">Someh Sara</string>
    <string name="fuman" translatable="false">Fuman</string>
    <string name="lahijan" translatable="false">Lahijan</string>
    <string name="langarud" translatable="false">Langarud</string>
    <string name="masal" translatable="false">Masal</string>

    <!--  lorestan  -->
    <string name="azna" translatable="false">Azna</string>
    <string name="aligudarz" translatable="false">Aligudarz</string>
    <string name="borujerd" translatable="false">Borujerd</string>
    <string name="poldokhtar" translatable="false">Poldokhtar</string>
    <string name="chegani" translatable="false">Chegani</string>
    <string name="khorram_abad" translatable="false">Khorram Abad</string>
    <string name="delfan" translatable="false">Delfan</string>
    <string name="dorud" translatable="false">Dorud</string>
    <string name="rumeshkan" translatable="false">Rumeshkan</string>
    <string name="selseleh" translatable="false">Selseleh</string>
    <string name="kuhdasht" translatable="false">Kuhdasht</string>

    <!--  mazandaran  -->
    <string name="amol" translatable="false">Amol</string>
    <string name="babol" translatable="false">Babol</string>
    <string name="babolsar" translatable="false">Babolsar</string>
    <string name="behshahr" translatable="false">Behshahr</string>
    <string name="tonekabon" translatable="false">Tonekabon</string>
    <string name="juybar" translatable="false">Juybar</string>
    <string name="chalus" translatable="false">Chalus</string>
    <string name="ramsar" translatable="false">Ramsar</string>
    <string name="sari" translatable="false">Sari</string>
    <string name="savad_kuh" translatable="false">Savad Kuh</string>
    <string name="north_savad_kuh" translatable="false">North Savad Kuh</string>
    <string name="simurgh" translatable="false">Simurgh</string>
    <string name="abbasabad" translatable="false">Abbasabad</string>
    <string name="fereydunkenar" translatable="false">Fereydunkenar</string>
    <string name="qaem_shahr" translatable="false">Qaem Shahr</string>
    <string name="kelardasht" translatable="false">Kelardasht</string>
    <string name="galugah" translatable="false">Galugah</string>
    <string name="mahmudabad" translatable="false">Mahmudabad</string>
    <string name="miandorud" translatable="false">Miandorud</string>
    <string name="neka" translatable="false">Neka</string>
    <string name="nour" translatable="false">Nour</string>
    <string name="nowshahr" translatable="false">Nowshahr</string>

    <!--  markazi  -->
    <string name="ashtiyan" translatable="false">Ashtiyan</string>
    <string name="arak" translatable="false">Arak</string>
    <string name="tafresh" translatable="false">Tafresh</string>
    <string name="khomeyn" translatable="false">Khomeyn</string>
    <string name="khondab" translatable="false">Khondab</string>
    <string name="delijan" translatable="false">Delijan</string>
    <string name="zarandieh" translatable="false">Zarandieh</string>
    <string name="saveh" translatable="false">Saveh</string>
    <string name="shazand" translatable="false">Shazand</string>
    <string name="farahan" translatable="false">Farahan</string>
    <string name="komijan" translatable="false">Komijan</string>
    <string name="mahallat" translatable="false">Mahallat</string>

    <!--  hormozgan  -->
    <string name="abu_musa" translatable="false">Abu Musa</string>
    <string name="bastak" translatable="false">Bastak</string>
    <string name="bashagard" translatable="false">Bashagard</string>
    <string name="bandar_lngeh" translatable="false">Bandar Lengeh</string>
    <string name="bandar_abbas" translatable="false">Bandar Abbas</string>
    <string name="parsiyan" translatable="false">Parsiyan</string>
    <string name="jask" translatable="false">Jask</string>
    <string name="hajiabad" translatable="false">Hajiabad</string>
    <string name="khamir" translatable="false">Khamir</string>
    <string name="rudan" translatable="false">Rudan</string>
    <string name="sirik" translatable="false">Sirik</string>
    <string name="qeshm" translatable="false">Qeshm</string>
    <string name="minab" translatable="false">Minab</string>

    <!--  hamedan  -->
    <string name="asadabad" translatable="false">Asadabad</string>
    <string name="bahar" translatable="false">Bahar</string>
    <string name="tuyserkan" translatable="false">Tuyserkan</string>
    <string name="darjazin" translatable="false">Darjazin</string>
    <string name="razan" translatable="false">Razan</string>
    <string name="famenin" translatable="false">Famenin</string>
    <string name="kabudarahang" translatable="false">Kabudarahang</string>
    <string name="malayer" translatable="false">Malayer</string>
    <string name="nahavand" translatable="false">Nahavand</string>


    <!--  yazd  -->
    <string name="abarkuh" translatable="false">Abarkuh</string>
    <string name="ardakan" translatable="false">Ardakan</string>
    <string name="ashkezar" translatable="false">Ashkezar</string>
    <string name="bafg" translatable="false">Bafg</string>
    <string name="behabad" translatable="false">Behabad</string>
    <string name="taft" translatable="false">Taft</string>
    <string name="harat" translatable="false">Harat</string>
    <string name="zarach" translatable="false">Zarach</string>
    <string name="marvast" translatable="false">Marvast</string>
    <string name="mehriz" translatable="false">Mehriz</string>
    <string name="meybod" translatable="false">Meybod</string>
</resources>